Data format:
UTF-8 encoding
1 row / subject
No labels


Column
1 to 128 = deck choice (from left to right, 0 = empty trial)
	min ? to max 128
129 to 256 = correct or not (1 or 0, -1 to be ignored)
257 ~ = other information

*
Parameter  boundaries
r = c(0, 1) #Reward feedback
p = c(0, 1) #Punished feedback
d = c(0.01, 5) #Decision consistency
i = c(0.01, 5) #Attentional focus

Model Names:
deckbase: no free parameter. Always .25 probability of choosing each deck
catt33: another baseline model. Constant .33 attention to each dimension.


----
*Sobol sequence:
low discrepancy sequence
	Discrepancy? 
Low-discrepancy sequences, also known as “quasirandom” sequences, are numbers that are better equidistributed in a given volume than pseudo-random numbers. 

*Stretching and contracting parameters: Why is it necessary? In MLE, bound problem exists
*Scaling parameters 3 to 2 or 2 to 3: why is it necessary?
*Scaling deck choice probability removing 1st trial: why remove?

Algorithms
Parameter setting:
	lb, ub: parbounds

Match matrices(constant):
	correctdeckmat
	matchstack

Scaling parameters: Scale what? attention weight?
	scale3to2
	scale2to3
	powerrize

Calculating predicted probabilities(attention weights):
	cattpredfun: assuming Constant ATTention weights. 각 덱 별로 얼마나 많은 dimension이 일치하는지에 따라 결정됨
	vattpredfun9: all purpose model
		1) for free pars, assign temporary assigned numbers from [temppars]
			for fixed pars, assign already fixed numbers from [fixedvals]
		2) Index which dimensions match current deck choice
		3) Based on correct or not(by r or p), calculated changed attention
		4) Based on the changed attention weight, calculated next deck choice probablity

Calculating model selection criteria
	cattG2fun: 
		1) for chosen deck, calculate matching attention to the choice
		2) Rescale the probablity removing 1st trial
		3) Calculate G2
	vattG2overarchfun:
		1) Contract pars
		2) calculate matching attention to the choice
		3) Rescale and calculate G2



Program body(loop across subjects):
1) Calculate G2, BIC for deckbase model and CATT model based on observed choices
2) Do iteration(across models)
	1) pick initial parameters from sobol sequence and stretch them
	2) optimize G2 with vattG2overarchfun and store the G2 at G2stack by each iteration
	3) store pars at parstack
		*for the first iteration, stack pars(contracted parameters that estimated through optim)at parstack 
		*for others, stack pars that has the minimum G2
3) Store minimum G2 , BIC and pars from iteration result



freeparsmat, fixedvalsmat, pequalsrmat, modnames: model category(or name) index
deckbaseG2, deckbaseBIC, catt33G2: subjnumx1, model selection criteria
	G2stack, BICstack: model selection criteria for each model, each iteration by subject
parstack: estimated pars for each model by subject
presobelmat: create random number and rescale in accordance with MLE par bounds





